wooglie.com 2019-04-22

# M2H » Privacy

Print this page

 Last modified: 26 April 2018, 12:07

This privacy policy applies to the information M2H B.V.(hereinafter referred to as “M2H” or “We”) collects about you when you register with us for our products, use the M2H websites, videogames, mobile applications, online store or other services (“Services”). “you” and “your” mean the user of our Services. In this policy, we want to be clear about the collection of your information. 

If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Services. Your continued use of the Services will signify your acceptance of these changes.

When using our Services some personal information about you is collected to provide a service you’ve requested or authorized: what information is collected depends on the product or service. Example of the information we collect:

 **Websites: Cookies**  
Our websites uses Cookies by Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). The information generated by the Cookies about your use of the Website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. We engage Google to do this in order to evaluate your use of the Website and compile reports on Website activity for us. We use this information to improve this and other websites.

For more information on the Cookies set by Google Analytics, including information on how to opt out, please visit [http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacypolicy.html](https://www.google.com/intl/en/privacypolicy.html). For more information on Cookies in general, please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>. You can block other advertising networks by visiting [http://www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/) if you are in Europe or <http://www.aboutads.info/> in US and Canada. To opt out of Google ads, visit [http://google.com/ads/preferences/](https://google.com/ads/preferences/).

 **Websites: Other**  
On some of our websites we have user registration forms. We may ask for your email address, your IP address and your self-chosen username and password. Extra information such as address, VAT, Company name might be needed to process payments.

 **Newsletters and competitions**  
For subscribing to a newsletter or when entering a giveaway/competition we may ask you for your personal information (Email address, full name). In the case of physical prizes, we may also need your (shipping) address.

 **NDA agreements**  
When we have a closed alpha/beta test of game, or any similar private activity, we may need you to sign a Non Disclosure Agreement contract. To make a legally binding contract possible, your full name and address will be required.

 **Games**  
Our games can transmit the following information:  
Diagnostic information (Including, but not limited to: Performance, System information such as operating system, resolution, crash dumps, log files, connection information, driver versions), user identification (Including, but not limited to: A platform ID such as a Steam User ID, Computer Name, IP address) information on the usage of the Service(Including, but not limited to: Screenshots, Chat logs and behavior on the service)

The purpose of the collection is to ensure safety, to analyse usage, improve and provide our services and to intervene in abuses. For example: an IP address is used to be able to identify and ban users in case of abuse and your e-mail address is used for identification and when you forget your password. 

M2H does not rent or sell your information to third parties for marketing or financial purposes. We can work with third parties to make your experience better, but our privacy policy doesn’t and can’t apply to those parties. We’re can not fully guarantee that other companies adhere to the same practices as us, so please be sure to read their policies and terms before sharing info with them.

To protect your personal data, M2H takes appropriate technical and organizational measures. For example: our servers are automatically updated against security threats and different services/games run on our own servers. We also use encryption and hashing for certain info we collect.

While we do our best to secure your data please note that no server or data transmission is fully secure. We can not guarantee the security of the data transmitted. By using our Services you are acknowledging that you are possibly sending your personal info at own risk.

Children under the age of sixteen should not register without the permission of a parent or guardian. By accepting this Privacy policy, you guarantee us that you are older than sixteen or that a parent/guardian gave you the permission to register.

This Privacy Policy shall be governed by the laws of The Netherlands and submitted to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in The Netherlands.

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy policy or its implementation, you may contact us: [privacy@M2H.nl](mailto:privacy@M2H.nl).

When you wish to adjust, correct, remove or hide your personal information, you may send us an e-mail: [privacy@M2H.nl](mailto:privacy@M2H.nl).

We reserve the right to make changes in this Privacy Policy, so please check back from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes. If there are significant changes in the way we collect or use your information, you’ll be notified prior to the implementation of the changes.

This Privacy Policy shall be governed by the laws of the Netherlands and submitted to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in the Netherlands.

M2H B.V.  
The Netherlands  
Chamber of Commerce: 66055210

© Copyright 2018 M2H B.V. All rights reserved.

 **Related links:**  
[https://www.M2H.nl/privacy](https://www.m2h.nl/privacy) (This page)
